Chee SIong Alex Chua

Citigold Acquisition Manager - 13 Years of Experience

SUMMARY

An individual who is self-motivated and has the desire to build a cordial relationship with co-workers. Humble, sincere, and always ready to learn, striving to improve to provide the best for others and himself. A team player who is focused on contributing in the best possible way. Strong desire of commitment towards achieving and maintaining a high level of standard in work.

In search for an opportunity to work and relocate overseas to experience a change in working culture and tradition.

BASIC INFORMATION

Birthday 28/01/1982
Nationality Foreigner
Maritality Married
Gender Male

LANGUAGES

Chinese (Mandarin) Advanced English Native

SKILLS

Banking Knowledge Excel Microsoft Office Access

CONTACT ME

alexyeu@icloud.com

6596889415

882 tampines street 84 s521882, International, Singapore

WORK HISTORY

Citigold Acquisition Manager

Citibank Singapore Limited 12/2020 - Current (1 year 4 months)

Acquiring Citigold and Citigold Private Clients with asset under management ranging between \$\$250,000 - \$\$1,499,999 and more than \$\$1,500,000 respectively. Utilising the bank resources and, working with internal and external partners to tap on various sources of acquisition. Sharing with prospects how our wealth management platform could assist them to attain their financial goal and achieve financial freedom using various financial tools available only for our wealth banking clients.

Citi Priority Acquisition Officer

Citibank Singapore Limited 01/2018 - 12/2020 (3 years)

Acquiring Citi Priority clients with asset under management ranging between S\$70,000 - S\$249,999. Facilitating the onboarding process, sharing the value propositions of our priority banking platform and providing timely assistance with regards to client's banking account.

Banking Acquisition Officer

Citibank Singapore Limited 04/2008 - 04/2016 (8 years 1 month)

Taking care of personal loans, credit cards and account opening for customers, Ensure total customer satisfaction through excellent after sales service. Performance is measure by commission base.

EDUCATION

Diploma in Mechatronics

High school - Temasek Polytechnic 01/2000 - 12/2001 (2 years)

Diploma in Mechatronics (Incomplete)

♦ O Levels

High school - Bedok South Secondary School 01/1995 - 01/1999 (4 years 1 month) GCE 5 "O" Levels

REFERENCES

Sanmaline Ng

Group Head - Citibank Singapore limited 93262688